



Projects

Ferrari Fitness

UX/UI Designer

Designed a cloud storage app for the fitness industry. Worked on all phases of the design process including Discovery, User Research, Information Architecture, Visual Design, and Testing.

SAP Project

Analyst at Bloomberg BNA

This project was transitioning our companies legacy Order Processing system to SAP. Conducted data analysis and performed various complex procedures with Excel and SQL queries. Assisted in testing for the new SAP order processing system.

Tax Treaty Project

Analyst at Bloomberg BNA

This project was creating a brand new tax database for all the tax treaties between each country in the world in every language. I performed User Research and Competitive Analysis to ensure the new product will meet end-user needs. Worked alongside various groups to deliver the project on time and within budget.

Education

Bloc San Francisco, CA (Remote)

UX/UI Design & Front-End Development Apprentice

APR 2018 - Present

Bloc is an immersive apprenticeship in UX/UI design and front-end development. Worked in partnership with multiple industry mentors in Bloc's respected curriculum. Designed web and mobile projects in multiple phases including discovery, strategy, information architecture, visual design, branding, and development.

George Mason University

B.S. Information Systems & Operations Management

Fairfax, VA 2012

Work Experience

Bloomberg BNA

Information Analyst

Bloomberg BNA

Data Analyst

APWU

Business Analyst

Right Start Consulting

Analyst

Crustal City, VA

JAN 2016 - Present

Crystal City, VA

FEB 2015 - NOV 2015

Washington D.C.

MAY 2014 - JAN 2015

Vienna, VA

SEP 2013 - FEB 2014

Design Skills

Sketching Wireframes Mockups **Prototypes**

User Personas Usability Testing User Flows User Surveys

ios **User Stories User Research Android**

Design Tools

Photoshop Illustrator Sketch

Balsamiq **Figma** MS Visio

Development Skills

HTML/CSS **JavaScript JQueru**

MS VBA SQL

Git/GitHub

Business Skills

Data Analysis Competitive Analysis Project Management Requirements Analysis

Branding

Business Tools

MS Excel (Advanced) MS Word MS PowerPoint MS Access Oracle SQL Developer **JIRA**

Google Sites Google Docs **Google Sheets** Google Forms Salesforce Tableau